(Sheldon:)Really, Amy?
(Sheldon:)Tobacco and alcohol?
(Sheldon:)Need I remind you not a lot of
scientific discoveries were made
(Sheldon:)by people having a good time?
(Amy:)Why did you bring him?
(Amy:)He's harshing my buzz.
(Penny:)I felt sorry for him.
(Penny:)Priya's giving him a hard time.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, the Priya bashing's
starting early. Yay!
(Bernadette:)Okay, what's up
with those pantsuits?
(Amy:)I need some context.
(Penny:)Pantsuits suck.
(Amy:)And that opens her up
(Amy:)to justifiable ridicule
for wearing them.
(Amy:)Good one, Bernadette.
See? Ca-razy.
Whee...!
(Amy:)You smell like baby powder.
(Sheldon:)It's talc.
(Sheldon:)But as that's a primary
ingredient of baby powder,
(Sheldon:)I understand your confusion.